Never surrender.
Surrounded is a western, action, drama film directed by Anthony Mandler.
After her stagecoach is ambushed, a woman is  tasked with holding a dangerous outlaw
captive and must survive the day when the bandit’s gang tries to free him.
Mo Washington, played by Letitia Wright.
Tommy Walsh, played by Jamie Bell.
Will Clay, played by Michael Kenneth Williams.
Wheeler, played by Jeffrey Donovan.
Curly, played by Kevin Wiggins.
Mr. Fields, played by Brett Gelman.
Surrounded is a 2023 American Western drama film directed by Anthony
Mandler and written by Andrew Pagana and Justin Thomas.
It stars Letitia Wright, Jamie Bell, Jeffrey Donovan,
Brett Gelman, and features Michael K.
Williams in his final appearance.
The film premiered at the Sun Valley Film Festival on April 2, 2023, and was
released digitally on June 20, 2023, by Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer Pictures.
The film explores themes of civil war, gold mine, outlaw, frontier, stagecoach.
The tone is emotional.